<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?> 
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"> 
		<channel> 
			<title>Study-Languages-Online.com</title> 
			<link>http://www.study-languages-online.com/</link> 
			<description>Russian language online: online courses, vocabulary topics, pronunciation training</description>
			<language>en</language>
			<copyright>Copyright 2009, Study-Languages-Online.com</copyright>  
			<managingEditor>study.languages.online@gmail.com</managingEditor>
			<item>
				<title>Article: Russian Indeclinable Nouns </title>
				<link>http://www.study-languages-online.com/russian-indeclinable-nouns.html</link>
				<description>
					Indeclinable nouns are nouns that don't display grammatical relations with other words in a sentence by means of declension. The paradigms of the indeclinable nouns contain a set of identical word forms, i.e. they do not inflect or change their forms for number and cases.
				</description>
			</item>
			<item>
				<title>Article: Russian Indefinite Pronouns </title>
				<link>http://www.study-languages-online.com/russian-indefinite-pronouns.html</link>
				<description>
					Indefinite pronouns are words used to refer to unknown, undetermined or intentionally unspecified beings, objects, properties and quantity. In Russian, this function is performed by several sets of pronouns formed from interrogative/relative pronouns.
				</description>
			</item>
			<item>
				<title>Article: Russian Negative Pronouns </title>
				<link>http://www.study-languages-online.com/russian-negative-pronouns.html</link>
				<description>
					Negative pronouns are words used to indicate the absence or non-existence of people, objects, or other entities.
				</description>
			</item>
			<item>
				<title>Article: Russian Reflexive Pronouns </title>
				<link>http://www.study-languages-online.com/russian-reflexive-pronouns.html</link>
				<description>
					Reflexive pronouns are words used to refer back to previously mentioned nouns and pronouns, most often to the subject of the sentence. In Russian, this function is generally performed by pronouns себя, свой and друг друга. 
				</description>
			</item>
			<item>
				<title>Flashcards</title>
				<link>http://www.study-languages-online.com/vocabulary.html?tab=2</link>
				<description>
					This is a new tool for learning Russian words and expressions on our website. Flashcards are designed to replace lexical exercises.
				</description>
			</item>
			<item>
				<title>Lexical tests redesign</title>
				<link>http://www.study-languages-online.com/vocabulary.html?tab=3</link>
				<description>
					We redesigned our lexical tests so that they are more interesting and useful.
				</description>
			</item>
			<item>
				<title>Russian Alphabet: Flashcards</title>
				<link>http://www.study-languages-online.com/alphabet-flashcard.html</link>
				<description>
					Online flashcards for learning Russian alphabet, with audio samples and quizzes.
				</description>
			</item>
			<item>
				<title>Article: Russian Demonstrative Pronouns </title>
				<link>http://www.study-languages-online.com/russian-determinative-pronouns.html</link>
				<description>
					Determinative pronouns are words used to emphasize nouns and pronouns. Their function is to define one or more objects in a class of similar ones. In Russian, this group of pronouns includes the words сам, самый, весь, всякий, каждый, иной, любой, другой, всяк, всяческий.
				</description>
			</item>
			<item>
				<title>Article: Non-past forms of irregular verbs </title>
				<link>http://www.study-languages-online.com/russian-irregular-verbs.html</link>
				<description>
					In Russian, there are only a few truly irregular verbs. They depart in various ways from regular conjugation patterns. Here you can find non-past forms of these verbs.
				</description>
			</item>
			<item>
				<title>New Topic: Telephone calls</title>
				<link>http://study-languages-online.com/telephone.html</link>
				<description>
					Russian online vocabulary for learning words and phrases related to the topic "Telephone calls"
				</description>
			</item>
			<item>
				<title>New Topic: Computer and Internet</title>
				<link>http://study-languages-online.com/computer.html</link>
				<description>
					Russian online vocabulary for learning words and phrases related to the topic "Computers and Internet"
				</description>
			</item>
			<item>
				<title>Short form of Russian adjectives</title>
				<link>http://study-languages-online.com/russian-adjectives-short.html</link>
				<description>
					Information about short forms of Russian adjectives: basic rules and particular instances, examples of usage
				</description>
			</item>
			<item>
				<title>Results of grammar exercises</title>
				<link>http://www.study-languages-online.com/russian-grammar.html</link>
				<description>
					Now our users can save their results of grammar exercises and review them in the section "My Results" in the Profile.  
				</description>
			</item>
			<item>
				<title>New section on our websiite: Russian grammar</title>
				<link>http://www.study-languages-online.com/russian-grammar.html</link>
				<description>
					This new section contains articles devoted to Russian grammar rules and grammar exercises.   
				</description>
			</item>
			<item>
				<title>Article: Russian Interrogative pronouns and adverbs </title>
				<link>http://www.study-languages-online.com/russian-interrogative-words.html</link>
				<description>
					Information about Russian most frequently used interrogative pronouns and adverbs with declension patterns and examples of usage.   
				</description>
			</item>
			<item>
				<title>Article: Declension of Russian adjectives </title>
				<link>http://www.study-languages-online.com/russian-adjectives-declension.html</link>
				<description>
					Information about the declension of Russian long-from adjectives: case endings and examples for declensions of differents types of adjectives.    
				</description>
			</item>
			<item>
				<title>Article: Russian cardinal numerals </title>
				<link>http://www.study-languages-online.com/russian-cardinal-numerals.html</link>
				<description>
					Information about Russian cardinal numerals: formation of simple and compound cardinal numerals.    
				</description>
			</item>
			<item>
				<title>Article: Plural forms of Russian nouns </title>
				<link>http://www.study-languages-online.com/russian-nouns-nominative-plural.html</link>
				<description>
					Information about nominative plural forms of Russian nouns: basic rules and particular cases.    
				</description>
			</item>
			<item>
				<title>Our page on Facebook.com</title>
				<link>http://www.facebook.com/pages/Study-Languages-Onlinecom/111268518902851</link>
				<description>
					We have created our page on Facebook.com. We plan to work with it in a similar way as we do with twitter.    
				</description>
			</item>
			<item>
				<title>Word Find Puzzle</title>
				<link>http://www.study-languages-online.com/crossword-game.html</link>
				<description>
					Classical word search puzzle. A very good practice for those who start to learn reading in Russian and a good opportunity to work on the vocabulary topics. Russian words are hidden randomly each time you try the puzzle, so you can play more than once.   
				</description>
			</item>
						
			<item>
				<title>Texts for reading practice</title>
				<link>http://www.study-languages-online.com/russian-reading-texts.html</link>
				<description>
					Here you will find texts in Russian designed for those who wish to have more practice in reading. Each text is accompanied by audio, transcription, translation and different settings options to demonstrate the most important points of Russian pronunciation. 
				</description>
			</item>
			<item>
				<title>Special tools which help in learning to read in Russian</title>
				<link>http://www.study-languages-online.com/reading-practice.html</link>
				<description>
					In lessons on reading in Russian, you can find special tools to highlight different groups of letters: letters denoting stressed vowels, reduced vowels, soft and unvoiced consonants. These tools may provide a great help to understand and learn basic rules of reading in Russian. 	
				</description>
			</item>
		</channel> 
</rss>

