<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?> 
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"> 
		<channel> 
			<title>Study-Languages-Online.com</title> 
			<link>http://www.study-languages-online.com/</link> 
			<description>Russian language online: online courses, vocabulary topics, pronunciation training</description>
			<language>en</language>
			<copyright>Copyright 2009, Study-Languages-Online.com</copyright>  
			<managingEditor>study.languages.online@gmail.com</managingEditor>
			<item>
				<title>Article: Declension of Russian adjectives </title>
				<link>http://www.study-languages-online.com/russian-adjectives-declension.html</link>
				<description>
					Information about the declension of Russian long-from adjectives: case endings and examples for declensions of differents types of adjectives.    
				</description>
			</item>
			<item>
				<title>Article: Russian cardinal numerals </title>
				<link>http://www.study-languages-online.com/russian-cardinal-numerals.html</link>
				<description>
					Information about Russian cardinal numerals: formation of simple and compound cardinal numerals.    
				</description>
			</item>
			<item>
				<title>Article: Plural forms of Russian nouns </title>
				<link>http://www.study-languages-online.com/russian-nouns-nominative-plural.html</link>
				<description>
					Information about nominative plural forms of Russian nouns: basic rules and particular cases.    
				</description>
			</item>
			<item>
				<title>Our page on Facebook.com</title>
				<link>http://www.facebook.com/pages/Study-Languages-Onlinecom/111268518902851</link>
				<description>
					We have created our page on Facebook.com. We plan to work with it in a similar way as we do with twitter.    
				</description>
			</item>
			<item>
				<title>Word Find Puzzle</title>
				<link>http://www.study-languages-online.com/crossword-game.html</link>
				<description>
					Classical word search puzzle. A very good practice for those who start to learn reading in Russian and a good opportunity to work on the vocabulary topics. Russian words are hidden randomly each time you try the puzzle, so you can play more than once.   
				</description>
			</item>
						
			<item>
				<title>Texts for reading practice</title>
				<link>http://www.study-languages-online.com/russian-reading-texts.html</link>
				<description>
					Here you will find texts in Russian designed for those who wish to have more practice in reading. Each text is accompanied by audio, transcription, translation and different settings options to demonstrate the most important points of Russian pronunciation. 
				</description>
			</item>
			<item>
				<title>Special tools which help in learning to read in Russian</title>
				<link>http://www.study-languages-online.com/reading-practice.html</link>
				<description>
					In lessons on reading in Russian, you can find special tools to highlight different groups of letters: letters denoting stressed vowels, reduced vowels, soft and unvoiced consonants. These tools may provide a great help to understand and learn basic rules of reading in Russian. 	
				</description>
			</item>
			<item>
				<title>User's Results for the Russian Course for Beginners</title>
				<link>http://www.study-languages-online.com/course.html#beginner_course</link>
				<description>
					Registered users can save and review their results of the tests and exercises in the Online Course for Beginners. We have also added lessons list of the online courses for a better navigation between lessons. The lessons list can be found in "Links and Settings" section in each lesson.
				</description>
			</item>
			<item>
				<title>Online Russian Course for Beginners</title>
				<link>http://www.study-languages-online.com/course.html#beginner_course</link>
				<description>
					A new free online course on our website. This course is designed for those who start learning Russian and would like to get basic language skills. Here you can learn Russian words and expressions used in greetings, farewells, requests, talking about yourself etc.
				</description>
			</item>
			<item>
				<title>Possibility to create User's Account</title>
				<link>http://www.study-languages-online.com/signup</link>
				<description>
					Our users can save and review their results of the tests and exercises now. See the Registration page
				</description>
			</item>
			<item>
				<title>Russian Demonstrative Pronouns</title>
				<link>http://www.study-languages-online.com/russian-demonstrative-pronouns.html</link>
				<description>
					Information about Russian demonstrative pronouns 'этот, тот': definition, peculiarities of usage, declension patterns.
				</description>
			</item>
			<item>
				<title>Gender of Russian nouns</title>
				<link>http://www.study-languages-online.com/russian-nouns-gender.html</link>
				<description>
					Information about gender of Russian nouns: characteristics of masculine, feminine and neuter nouns, basic rules to determine the gender of a noun.
				</description>
			</item>
			<item>
				<title>Russian Possessive Pronouns</title>
				<link>http://www.study-languages-online.com/russian-possessive-pronouns.html</link>
				<description>
					Information about Russian possessive pronouns and reflexive possessive pronoun: description, peculiarities of usage, declension patterns.
				</description>
			</item>
			<item>
				<title>Gender in Russian</title>
				<link>http://study-languages-online.com/russian-personal-pronouns.html</link>
				<description>
					Gender is a grammatical category used in Russian for the classification of nouns, pronouns, adjectives and certain verb forms into three classes: masculine, feminine and neuter. 
				</description>
			</item>
			<item>
				<title>Russian Personal Pronouns</title>
				<link>http://study-languages-online.com/russian-personal-pronouns.html</link>
				<description>
					Personal pronouns are words used in place of a noun to indicate the speaker, the person to whom one is speaking, and persons and objects spoken about. Russian personal pronouns distinguish three persons, two numbers, six cases, and, in the third person, three genders.
				</description>
			</item>
			<item>
				<title>Russian Nouns Declension</title>
				<link>http://study-languages-online.com/russian-nouns-declension.html</link>
				<description>
					In Russian, almost all nouns decline, i.e. change their endings to express a particular case. They decline according to certain patterns that form large groups called declensions. There a 3 declension types in Russian: first declension (I declension), second declension (II declension) and third declension (III declension).
				</description>
			</item>
			<item>
				<title>Animacy in Russian</title>
				<link>http://study-languages-online.com/russian-animate-inanimate.html</link>
				<description>
					In Russian, animacy is a characteristic of nouns which indicates that the meaning of the word correlates to a living being. Based on this characteristic, all Russian nouns are divided into two classes: animate nouns that have human or animal referents and inanimate nouns that refer to nonliving objects and abstract things.	
				</description>
			</item>


			


		</channel> 
</rss>

