<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?> 
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"> 
		<channel> 
			<title>Study-Languages-Online.com</title> 
			<link>http://www.study-languages-online.com/</link> 
			<description>Russian language online: online courses, vocabulary topics, pronunciation training</description>
			<language>en</language>
			<copyright>Copyright 2009, Study-Languages-Online.com</copyright>  
			<managingEditor>study.languages.online@gmail.com</managingEditor>
			<item>
				<title>Possibility to create User's Account</title>
				<link>http://www.study-languages-online.com/signup</link>
				<description>
					Our users can save and review their results of the tests and exercises now. See the Registration page
				</description>
			</item>
			<item>
				<title>Russian Demonstrative Pronouns</title>
				<link>http://www.study-languages-online.com/russian-demonstrative-pronouns.html</link>
				<description>
					Information about Russian demonstrative pronouns 'этот, тот': definition, peculiarities of usage, declension patterns.
				</description>
			</item>
			<item>
				<title>Gender of Russian nouns</title>
				<link>http://www.study-languages-online.com/russian-nouns-gender.html</link>
				<description>
					Information about gender of Russian nouns: characteristics of masculine, feminine and neuter nouns, basic rules to determine the gender of a noun.
				</description>
			</item>
			<item>
				<title>Russian Possessive Pronouns</title>
				<link>http://www.study-languages-online.com/russian-possessive-pronouns.html</link>
				<description>
					Information about Russian possessive pronouns and reflexive possessive pronoun: description, peculiarities of usage, declension patterns.
				</description>
			</item>
			<item>
				<title>Gender in Russian</title>
				<link>http://study-languages-online.com/russian-personal-pronouns.html</link>
				<description>
					Gender is a grammatical category used in Russian for the classification of nouns, pronouns, adjectives and certain verb forms into three classes: masculine, feminine and neuter. 
				</description>
			</item>
			<item>
				<title>Russian Personal Pronouns</title>
				<link>http://study-languages-online.com/russian-personal-pronouns.html</link>
				<description>
					Personal pronouns are words used in place of a noun to indicate the speaker, the person to whom one is speaking, and persons and objects spoken about. Russian personal pronouns distinguish three persons, two numbers, six cases, and, in the third person, three genders.
				</description>
			</item>
			<item>
				<title>Russian Nouns Declension</title>
				<link>http://study-languages-online.com/russian-nouns-declension.html</link>
				<description>
					In Russian, almost all nouns decline, i.e. change their endings to express a particular case. They decline according to certain patterns that form large groups called declensions. There a 3 declension types in Russian: first declension (I declension), second declension (II declension) and third declension (III declension).
				</description>
			</item>
			<item>
				<title>Animacy in Russian</title>
				<link>http://study-languages-online.com/russian-animate-inanimate.html</link>
				<description>
					In Russian, animacy is a characteristic of nouns which indicates that the meaning of the word correlates to a living being. Based on this characteristic, all Russian nouns are divided into two classes: animate nouns that have human or animal referents and inanimate nouns that refer to nonliving objects and abstract things.	
				</description>
			</item>
			<item>
				<title>Articulation of Russian vowels - completed!</title>
				<link>http://study-languages-online.com/russian-articulation.html</link>
				<description>
					On this page you can find: description and audio samples of all basic Russian sounds. You can choose several modes modes to view the descriptions: by sound, by category or all sounds. Some updates will possibly come in future, but in general all the functionality of the page is ready.

				</description>
			</item>

			<item>

				<title>Articulation of Russian vowels</title>
				<link>http://study-languages-online.com/russian-articulation.html</link>
				<description>
					Descriptions of Russian hard consonant sounds have been added to the page.
				</description>
			</item>
			<item>
				<title>Prepositional case of Russian nouns</title>

				<link>http://study-languages-online.com/russian-prepositional-case.html</link>
				<description>
					The prepositional case is a set of word forms which usually mark the location of the action. The prepositional case word forms are used in Russian only together with prepositions.	
				</description>
			</item>
			<item>
				<title>Instrumental case of Russian nouns</title>
				<link>http://study-languages-online.com/russian-instrumental-case.html</link>

				<description>
					The instrumental case is a set of word forms which usually mark the means of the action, like the English preposition "with" in phrase "he is writing with a pen".
				</description>
			</item>
			<item>
				<title>Accusative case of Russian nouns</title>
				<link>http://study-languages-online.com/russian-accusative-case.html</link>
				<description>

					The accusative case is a set of word forms which usually mark the object of the action, like the English word "letter" in the phrase "he is writing a letter".
				</description>
			</item>

		</channel> 
</rss>

